lorigeurin.com 2017-10-07

# PRIVACY POLICY - LORI GEURIN

## Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 27, 2016

At LoriGeurin.com we take your privacy very seriously. We created this privacy policy to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you provide on our website.

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Information Collection And Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name and email address.

### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends when you visit our Site (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third-party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this information.

### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters or promotional materials.

### About Cookies

Cookies are files with small amounts of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Also, cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to show when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to website users based on their visit to the site and/or other sites on the internet.

Users may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. But please remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 27, 2016. It will stay in effect, except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will go into effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time. You should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the changes and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://www.lorigeurin.com/contact/).
